[Music]
at the heart of tun Raza exchange a
world-class and exciting commercial
development manera Prudential stands
proud as the latest chapter in
prudential malaysia' x' years of
excellence in the country housing all
four business units Prudential Assurance
Malaysia Berhad Prudential BSN takaful
Berhad East spring investments per head
and prudential services Asia it is
indeed an iconic landmark which
symbolizes credentials expertise as
Malaysia's leading insurance and asset
management provider with all of its
businesses in Malaysia under one roof
menara Prudential promises to foster
closer working relationships and synergy
translating into greater speed and value
for customers when it came to the
interior design what mats of great
leader Prudential was showcasing
Malaysia's rich diversity culture and
heritage while seamlessly incorporating
modern and innovative elements three
themes were chosen to best express the
richness and beauty of Malaysia natural
scenery urban landscape and arts and
culture natural scenery depicts the
natural beauty of Malaysia with
collaboration areas based on distinct
sites such as mount kinabalu taman
negara
[Music]
interacting beach the urban landscape
design features modern and contemporary
elements such as street art playground
and even a library and of course to
represent Malaysia's diversity the arts
and culture theme played on tradition
and heritage the cafes are modeled after
a mama a war room and the collaboration
areas feature design elements that
incorporate why young Khalid songket and
traditional games just to name a few
infusing these distinctive local
elements create a workplace with heart
and soul resonating the credentials
proud heritage and history in Malaysia
manera Prudential is designed to promote
an agile and collaborative work
environment the fitting credential
status as a modern and innovative
industry trendsetter the interior
features thematic contemporary design
furnished with agile workspaces over 10
types of workplace settings suited for
activity-based working
[Music]
for example there are open collaboration
areas and work cafes for group
discussions focus pods and flex offices
offer more privacy and a space to do
individual focused work while height
adjustable desks enable the user to work
standing or sitting employees can enjoy
the flexibility of the various work
environments depending on their needs
and nature of work it all adds up to a
corporate culture of constant
connectivity innovation and progress
Prudential has leveraged on the power of
technology to create a conducive
environment for its people to excel all
floors are furnished with the latest
state-of-the-art technology to enhance
and promote productivity and quality
other amenities such as a multi-purpose
Hall for employee events and a childcare
center are available on the ground floor
the retail branch features modern design
elements for an enriching customer
experience manera Prudential is a
landmark and icon more importantly it
marks a milestone in credentials journey
as Malaysia's leading insurance and
asset management provider this is where
amazing new success stories will be
written koreas will be built and lives
will be transformed welcome to the
all-new manera Prudential Anton Reza
exchange
you
[Music]